DC public schools told my
parents back in kindergarten that
I was unedigable, male retargeted,
emotionally disturbed and really not
much could be done about
it.
And your mom said, forget
about it, this kid's smart.
They went out and got
a top of the line
psychoeducational evaluation of me from
George Washington University. And those
evaluators met with my parents
and said that I had
strephosymbolia and acute hyperkinetic disorder,
acute hyperkinetic, adult dyslexic. That
is the product of intense
early intervention from this best.
And they would say, you
know, I want what is
best for my child. And
of course, as parents, we
all do.
But if you say that
at a meeting, you have
now closed the door to
your child getting quality services,
because by law, by case
law, by statute, your child
is not entitled to what
is best. Your child's only
entitled to what's called a
free, appropriate stop. I put
my hand up, right? I'd
reach my hand across the
table and right to almost
to their face. I wanted
to create a visceral gut
reaction to that word best.
I wanted it paired with
somebody coming and putting their
hand in their face. And
so that they stopped saying
it before it even came
out of the mouse, because
they knew that was a
four letter word in Spanish.
I love it. It's a
four letter word. Best is
a four letter word. If
you want to get quality
services for your child, that's
a four letter word. Don't
ever use that. And talk
about for people that don't
understand what faith is free
and appropriate.